sanmecrusher.com 2019-05-03

# SANME Privacy Policyt - SANME

###  Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before using this website 

Sanme(Shanghai Sanme Mining Machinery Co.,Ltd) takes very seriously the privacy of the Site users and the security of your personal information. It is Sanme's aim that you, if your personal information is processed by Sanme, at all times shall feel confident that your privacy is respected and that due care is taken regarding your personal information. 

The purpose of this statement is to set out the principles governing Sanme's use of personal information that Sanme obtains about you. By accessing the Site you agree to the following terms. If you do not agree to them, you should not use the Site. 

Sanme will comply with national data protection laws that govern the collection and use of personal information, and which will apply to the activities of Sanme. Under national data protection laws you have rights of access and rectification in relation to your personal information. Sanme will adhere to such rights as far as possible to fulfill Sanme's legal obligations. 

Sanme collects personal information such as first name, last name, e-mail address and country of residence and other information that is voluntarily submitted by the users of the Site. The personal information provided by you will be processed for the purpose of providing the information and services you request as well as for marketing, sales and product development purposes. Sanme may give personal information to third parties, located within as well as outside the European Union, such as a distributor of our products in order to process your orders and fulfill your requests. 

**Cookies**  
When you view one of our websites, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" and will help us better serve you. Cookies are small text files that a website transfers to your browser, which may then store the cookie on your hard drive. Any information gathered by the use of cookies is compiled on an aggregate, anonymous basis. Cookies cannot contain virus or harmful program code. It does not require large space on your hard drive and can be deleted. 

This information allows us to measure site activity and to tailor information to suit your individual preferences, for example subscription of news. The goal is to save you time and provide you with a more meaningful visit. By showing how and when our visitors use this website, this information can help us to improve our website on a continual basis. 

If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so. In Netscape you find these settings in Edit / Preferences / Privacy & Security (Advanced in older versions) and in Internet Explorer in Tools / Internet Options / Security (Privacy or Advanced in older versions). 

Sanme does not assume any responsibility for the privacy practices or the contents of external websites to which the Site contain links. 

Sanme may at any time revise the terms of this Privacy Policy by updating it. 

If you have any questions regarding Sanme's processing of your personal information, you are welcome to contact us.  
Tel: +86-21-57121166  
Fax: +86-21-58200089  
E-mail: service@sanmecrusher.com
